<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hilario for 25</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hilario for 25</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Housing as a Human Right</title>
      <link>/issues/housing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/issues/housing/</guid>
      <description>Equitable access to affordable, high quality housing, infrastructure, and community resources is essential for both individual and community well being. In the 25th Ward in particular, money from luxury real estate developers has taken over our political establishment - leading to rezonings that favor costly residences and amenities, pushing out small businesses and working families.
So what do we do?
The first step is simply recognizing housing as a human right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equitable Progress and Development</title>
      <link>/issues/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/issues/development/</guid>
      <description>Our ward is filled with vibrant neighborhoods that have been built by the residents, not developers. The residents of our community have already proven time and time again that they’re the best placed people to make decisions about development in our ward and neighborhoods. Hilario will use his authority as alderman to ensure that zoning and development decisions are transparent and democratic, countering attempts by moneyed interests to place profits over people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environmental Justice</title>
      <link>/issues/environmental-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/issues/environmental-justice/</guid>
      <description>In Chicago, especially in areas on the southwest side like the 25th Ward, profit has long been prioritized over the health of people. Families and the 25th Ward are facing public health crises from pollution in the air they breathe to lead in the water they drink, because politicians have chosen corporate donations over communities and families.
As alderman, Hilario will…
 Fight to shut down toxic industrial enterprises like the Fisk Power Plant, which threaten the health of residents of the 25th Ward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fair Elections</title>
      <link>/issues/fair-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/issues/fair-elections/</guid>
      <description>Every citizen deserves an equal voice in the governance decisions that affect their daily lives. But when elections are awash in big-dollar donations from private interests and profit-driven corporations, our communities’ voices end up drowned out. Reviving the core values of American democracy require us to demand expanded transparency, genuine fairness, and proven integrity.
As alderman, Hilario will&amp;hellip;
 Advocate for the Fair Elections Ordinance, which ensures that our elections are citizen- and voter-funded by establishing a small-donor matching fund that is available to candidates who agree to spending limits and restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>